Do you want to hear a story?
Do you want me to tell you
about the Wildling?
His teeth are long...
...and sharp like this.
And so are his nails.
Long and sharp...
...like this.
And his hair...
...is long and black.
All over his whole body.
Do you wanna hear more?
No.
Okay.
You're my special little berry.
- Good morning, Anna.
- Good morning, Daddy.
I'm gonna listen to your heart
and I'm gonna tell you to breathe.
Okay, now.
Breathe in.
Okay.
The men are getting worried.
They don't see you around anymore.
Hunt's over.
Sure, but that don't mean
you can just disappear.
Roger, I'm retired.
Alright. I'll see yo...
I'm sorry the door gave you a sting.
I told you about that.
It's made so that the Wildling
will get hurt if he tries to get in.
Why does he wanna get in?
Because you're the last one left.
He ate all the other children.
Who was that today?
I heard someone talking.
There is no one.
There is only Anna and Daddy.
Anna and Daddy.
But only Daddy can go outside...
...because Anna is too small.
Anna must always stay inside.
Anna must stay inside.
# Happy birthday to you
# Happy birthday, dear Anna ##
Close your eyes. Okay, now open.
I plucked him from the berry-bush.
"Was evident...
"...that the youngster had become so accus...
- Accustomed.
- "Accustomed...
...to the marvelous..."
One, two, three, four...
...five, six, seven, eight...
Seven, eight, nine, ten.
He's in a better place.
I'm gonna take him to where I plucked him...
...and I'm going to bury him there...
...and then after a while...
...a bush will grow out of him...
...and then when the spring comes...
...it'll grow new berries.
And Dusty will grow back?
Yes...
...but it will be a new Dusty.
What's wrong with me?
You're sick.
Anna, this is medicine...
...and Daddy needs to see your tummy.
Good girl. Now Daddy is gonna
put the medicine in your tummy...
...and it's gonna sting, okay?
Anna, close your eyes. Now, one...
...two...
...three.
Good girl.
We're gonna have to do this every day.
Hey, Anna. Anna.
It's your birthday.
Don't you wanna count your bears?
Daddy...
...can...
...can you take me to the better place?
Maybe a bush will grow out of me.
You'll close your eyes...
...and you'll go to sleep.
Then there will be nothing.
No.
Very good, we're pushing 1000 milligrams.
Hi.
It's okay.
I'm here to help you.
I'm the one who found you.
Your neighbors called me to report a gunshot.
Sheriff Ellen Cooper.
I have a few questions to ask you.
Would that be okay?
Yeah?
What's your name?
Anna.
Anna. It's nice to meet you, Anna.
What's your last name?
Anna.
Officer...
...can I talk with you for a minute?
You sit tight.
We detected a high concentration
of Leuprorelin in her system.
One more day and we probably
would've lost her.
- What's that?
- It's typically used to treat...
...endometriosis uterine fibroids
or conditions such as paraphilia.
Thing is, she's got none of those.
In fact, we couldn't find anything
to justify this kind of treatment.
Do you think he was poisoning her?
Uh, it's a pretty heavy drug...
...with a wide range of drastic side
effects, but it is very efficient...
...at down-regulating the secretion
of estrogen in a woman's body.
There is no evidence
of any menstrual cycle at all.
I think whoever did this to her
wants to slow down her maturity.
- That's fucked up.
- Yeah, I'll leave you to it.
- Thank you, doctor.
- Yeah.
Anna...
...I'm gonna undo these straps for you, okay?
It's okay.
Just gonna undo these straps.
Like that.
It's okay.
There you go.
Where's Daddy?
Is he in the better place?
Good morning, everyone.
So the doctors have told me
what a bright young girl you are...
...and how well you've responded over
the past week to all their crazy tests.
I bet you're just about ready
to get out of here, huh?
Well, we think you're ready to move on too.
So the Belington House is a wonderful place.
They have a wide variety
of special therapeutic programs...
...designed for girls just like you
and it's a lot more fun than a hospital.
Excuse me, I'm sorry to interrupt...
...but I gotta say, locking her up again
doesn't really sound like the right strategy.
With all due respect, Sheriff,
I think we can trust Dr. Rooney's expertise.
We haven't even received the DNA results yet.
I was just explaining to our patient,
the Belington House is...
I'm gonna go with her!
Well, uh...
...we'll see about that.
So you're gonna be with me
until your DNA results come in.
DNA is something that we use to identify
any relatives that you might have.
Until then I'm gonna be responsible for you.
You okay with that?
You don't like my driving?
We're going less
than 20 miles an hour. It's safe.
I mean, not in... in general.
If, you know, for example if you're
driving under the influence but...
...I don't drink so no need
to worry about that.
- You don't drink?
- Not anymore.
You must be very thirsty.
Not many vegetarians in this town.
Little shit.
- What are you thinking?
- Come on, let's go.
You wanna stay away from guys like that.
You hungry?
I'm not a great cook,
but I know what goes with ketchup.
Pretty good, huh?
- Who's this?
- Anna, this is Ray.
Ray, this is Anna, the girl that I was
telling you about from the hospital.
Why is she wearing my clothes?
Because she's our guest and because
she needed something to wear.
You never wear that shirt anyway,
so why do you care?
- What happened to your head?
- It's none of your fuckin' business.
Excuse me, language, young man.
Are you his Daddy?
No, I'm not his daddy. I'm his sister.
Only men can be daddies and women are moms.
Everyone has them.
Whether you like it or not.
I'm sorry it smells a bit musty in here...
...because we don't use this room very often.
Okay, here you go.
Well if you, uh, you need anything,
I'm just across the hall, okay?
Okay?
- Can we close it?
- Are you cold?
The Wildling.
What's the Wildling?
He eats children.
Oh.
Did your daddy tell you that?
Have you ever seen him, a Wildling?
In my dreams.
Listen, Anna, I've been to a lot of places...
...and I've never seen a Wildling before.
It's okay, you're safe here.
You get some rest. You've had a long day.
Goodnight.
Hey.
Good morning.
You okay in there?
It's 7:00, time for breakfast.
Whoa!
We only moved here for Ellen's job.
Right after our parents died.
If we were still in the city,
we'd be taking the subway.
No subway sucks.
No cell phone signal anywhere, ever. Sucks.
Only one single chain restaurant
and that's Dairy Queen. Sucks.
I told you.
They're not hamsters.
And they're not babies either.
No?
Do you wanna see where you really come from?
Well, this should give you the general idea.
Got a little something for you.
You know, that's what you use
when you're bleeding down there.
- So it's medicine?
- No. No, no, you're not sick.
You're a woman.
Whoo, go Lady Grizzlies!
- Do you know where the library is?
- Yeah, I'll show you.
The party is this Saturday.
It's at my house.
So you should definitely come
'cause you'll get to meet everyone.
- Gonna be super fun.
- Thank you.
Bye.
Oh, God, really?
Yeah, I mean probably.
She's barefoot.
You think she's the girl
who was kept in her father's attic?
- Oh, my God, really, like a sex slave?
- Yeah.
She must be retarded.
Uh, hi. Excuse me, miss. Hi.
You lookin' for something?
I'm looking for Ray. He was supposed
to meet me at the library after school...
You know, you should really be more careful,
there's like broken glass and shit.
We might be able to help you out.
- Come on, let me out!
- What you think?
Sure.
- You guys are so hilarious.
- Ray, you never told us you had a girlfriend.
- I don't.
- Then what are you, fuck-buddies?
- Leave her out of this.
- Hey, buddy.
You forgot something.
- Who's smokin' pot?
- No one.
Oh, good boy. That's a good boy.
- Make sure he remembers that.
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, that was very impressive.
What's your name?
You're not doing me any favors.
You always go up like this against the grain.
My dad taught me how to do this.
He used to shave
every single day of his life.
Not his legs. His face.
Anna, there is something
that I need to talk to you about.
Those DNA tests came back.
They show that Gabriel Hanson
is not your real father.
He's not your Daddy.
What?
Do you remember what I said
about moms and dads?
- Everyone has 'em.
- Yeah.
We're still not sure
who your real mom and dad are.
I don't think the state's gonna
let you stay with me forever.
We're gonna have to find you
a more permanent home.
You can't escape so easily.
The test is Monday and you've only
gone through half of your stuff.
So?
What do you know about
the Declaration of Independence?
Come on, if you flunk this
Ellen is gonna kill me.
Have you ever been to the Northern Lights?
- No, you can't see them from here.
- Why?
'Cause they're really, really far north
where there's no more people.
I'd actually like to see
the Northern Lights too.
My mom...
...she showed me pictures when I was like...
...this.
Uh... what are you doing?
You smell.
I smell?
Like a hamburger.
I've never got that one before.
What's that?
What?
There.
I think Jen is having a party.
I know Jen.
How do you know her?
She's my friend.
- Hey, where you guys goin'?
- To a party.
Uh, you don't wanna party with me?
I thought we were gonna fire up the grill.
Yeah, but couldn't we do that tomorrow?
- Yeah, sure.
- Why don't you come to the party?
I don't think Ellen would wanna
come to this kinda party.
- What kind of party is "This kinda party?"
- It's at Jen's house.
Yeah, were gonna be home before midnight.
Hi. Who are you again?
Anna.
- Anna. Come on in.
- Thank you.
You're with a girl. Good for you.
Hey, buddy.
- Why didn't you bring your mommy?
- She's my sister, asshole.
Oh, wow, I didn't know
you could fart out of your mouth.
Hidden talents, man. Hidden talents.
Here. Don't drink it too fast.
That's great.
Anna. Anna, what's the matter?
Anna, I can take you home.
Come out and let's go.
Anna?
Anna. Anna, can you please open the door?
It's made...
...so that the Wildling
will get hurt if he tries to get in.
Why does he wanna get in?
Because you're the last one left.
He ate all the other children.
Anna!
Are you okay? Where have you been?
Anna, did someone hurt you?
Come.
Ray and I have been looking
for you everywhere.
Anna, listen, I...
...I want you to know
that you can trust me, okay?
You can tell me anything.
I really need to know
what happened last night.
Where you've been
and what happened to your dress.
Did someone try and hurt you
or touch you in any way?
- Roger.
- You need any help with her?
- No, I'm fine, thank you.
- Well, here's the thing.
Richard Fuller just called
and his 18-year-old son Lawrence...
...was also at that party
and he didn't come home either.
He was last seen around 11:00 p.m.
Tom and I asked the kids,
but no one seems to see him leave, so...
- Well, I thought maybe we should ask her.
- I think you should let me handle that.
Anna, you need to talk to me.
Anna, you need to tell me
what happened at that party last night.
You don't wanna be painting your nails
right now. I'm trying to help you.
- I can't help you if you won't talk to me.
- Ellen.
What's going on? Are you okay?
Ray, what do you know about Lawrence Fuller?
- You mean besides being an asshole?
- Well, that asshole is missing.
You think that Anna has something to do
with this? Is that what's going on here?
I want her to tell me where
she was last night. She won't talk.
Ellen, I think it would be better
if I talk to her.
- Oh, you do? Yeah?
- Yes, alone. Yeah.
Thank you.
Don't worry, I won't tell her
about the blood.
Anna, you can't do stuff like this.
How am I supposed to protect you?
Let me see.
Ellen!
- Ellen!
- Yeah?
We need to take her to the hospital.
Thought so.
You're looking for the others...
...like you.
I haven't seen
one of your kind in 16 years...
...since the last purge.
Yeah.
I remember that night.
I'll never forget it.
Men from the town said
they got every last one of them.
But that isn't quite true, is it?
Do you wanna know where your mother is?
Gabe, you okay?
I'm fine!
Any more of them bastards back there?
No, we got 'em all.
Every last one of them.
You're my special little berry.
- What's going on?
- We found Lawrence...
...and her dress by his body.
I'm sorry, Anna.
I really wanna understand.
I'll be back.
- Goodnight, Roger.
- Goodnight.
Before I got you...
...I had a dog.
His name was Jasper. Good dog.
Always a bit of a rebel.
But then after the night I got you...
...Jasper got crazier and crazier.
And then finally one day he snapped.
So I had to send him to the better place...
...you know.
I swore an oath, Anna.
That I would kill the Wildlings.
If I had been...
...half the true hunter Jasper was...
...there would be no Anna...
...and Jasper would still be at my side.
There's a better place for you.
Lift up your shirt.
Find the place...
...and put it in.
Now, push it in. Push it all the way in.
Daddy...
...why didn't you tell me
that I'm a Wildling?
I wanted to spare you.
Why?
Why did you spare me?
Anna was a mistake...
...and so is Daddy.
Roger.
Good morning, Anna.
You okay under there?
Come on, get up, I need
to take you to the district...
Ah! No! No!
Anna!
Anna?
Drive!
- Anna, seriously...
- Can you go a bit quicker, please?
- Where are we even going?
- To the Northern Light.
Seriously? This is crazy.
I mean, you're a fugitive.
No, I'm a Wildling.
Why are you slowing down?
Why are we stopping?
- What is it, a Wildling?
- Keep driving!
What is a Wildling, Anna? I wanna help you...
...but you can't honestly think that
we can just steal a cop car like this.
They can trace this thing!
Hey. Hey, Wildling!
Aw, fuck, that's cold.
You're gonna get sick in those wet clothes.
Hey.
Come on, Anna. Get up.
Raise your arms.
I won't bite you.
You track her down?
Get the men.
I can't do that, Gabe.
Not if she's with the kid.
I ran into Cooper this mornin'.
I tell ya she's asking too many questions.
I'm not going to jail for this, Gabe.
Not for your mist...
You let her get away!
It's not that bad, really.
It won't stay like this.
What is it?
- Run.
- What?
Ray, stay down.
Come.
- You gotta jump!
- What?
If we follow the river, it's probably
gonna take us back to the lake.
From there, we can find our way back
to the car and find Ellen.
Come on, let's go.
Ellen.
Ray!
Oh, my God.
- Who did this to you?
- No fucking idea.
Where is Anna?
Gone.
Over there.
Let's head over this way.
...the lead suspect in the murder
of fellow high school class mate...
...Lawrence Fuller. Fuller was found
dead at a party three months ago...
...and his killer is still at large.
Anna was arrested shortly after the murder
but escaped and is still missing...
...several months into the investigation.
An important warning,
authorities are urging residents...
...not to take matters
into their own hands...
...as they fear this female
suspect may be dangerous.
She has been linked to...
- Watch where you're going.
- I'm sorry.
We gotta go.
Now.
Go, go, go!
- Ray?
- Ellen, where are you?
- Fern Creek. Why?
- Listen, listen, they're on the move.
And Roger's with them.
Whoa!
She killed him.
Come on. Move! Move!
Watch your step, Sheriff.
Put it down.
Put it down!
You shouldn't have been snoopin' around
and you should've never taken that girl.
You're never gonna get...
This is 185 to dispatch. I need backup.
Copy please.
You got a new little berry.
It's almost ripe.
Soon you will be in the better place.
It's okay.
Alright. Almost, almost.
Alright, come on.
Come on.
Come on, that's it.
That's it.
There.
It's alright.
That's it.
I promise ya...
...if it's a girl...
...I'll name it Anna.
Ellen.